Register of the George Sokolsky Papers, 1916-1962
Hoover Institution Archives
- CORRESPONDENCE, 1916-1962
  - Dewavrin, Bernard, 1951 (Folder 3)
  - Dewey, Thomas, 1941-1951. Includes correspondence with Guy Graves, James C. Hagerty, and Paul Lockwood (Folder 4)
  - De Witt Clinton High School, 1944-1959 (Folder 5)
  - Dickinson, John, 1943-1952 (Folder 6)
  - Dickson, Alice M.
    - 1940-1944 (Folder 7)
    - 1945-1947 (Folder 8)
    - 1948-1960 (Folder 9)
  - Dirksen, Everett M., 1951 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Disney, Walt, 1955 (Folder 2)
  - Ditmars, Walter E., 1954 (Folder 3)
  - Dodd, John J., 1946-1950 (Folder 4)
  - Dodd, Thomas J., 1958-1962 (Folder 5)
  - Dohrenwend, Otto, 1948-1952 (Folder 6)
  - Dollar, Harold, 1921-1924 (Folder 7)
  - Donald, W. H.
    - 1920 (Folder 8)
    - 1921 (Folder 9)
    - 1922-1929 (Folder 10)
  - Donner, Robert, 1950-1951 (Folder 11)
  - Donovan, Thomas J., 1961 (Folder 12)
  - Doubleday, Doran and Company, 1932-1942 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Douglas, L. W., 1951-1953 (Folder 2)
  - Downes, James R.
    - 1941-1944 (Folder 3)
    - 1945-1946 (Folder 4)
    - 1947-1952 (Folder 5)
  - Downey, Morton, 1949-1961 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Downs, William H., 1959 (Folder 2)
  - Dowty, Leonhard, 1947-1948 (Folder 3)
  - Doyle, Eugene T., 1954-1959 (Folder 4)
  - Draught, James M., 1942-1943 (Folder 5)
  - Driskill, John, 1954-1955 (Folder 6)
  - Drysdale, W. S., 1919-1921 (Folder 7)
  - Dubinsky, David, 1941-1949 (Folder 8)
  - Duell, Sloan and Pearce, Inc., 1950-1952 (Folder 9)
  - Duffy, Charles G., 1948-1949 (Folder 10)
  - Duggan, Stephen P., 1925-1933 (Folder 11)
  - Dulles, Allen, 1953-1956 (Folder 12)
  - Dulles, John Foster, 1945-1958 (Folder 13)
  - Duncan, Robert, 1961 (Folder 14)
  - Dunn, Rogers C., 1945-1950 (Folder 15)
  - Du Pont, Lammot, 1939-1947 (Folder 16)
  - Durant, Will, 1929-1937 (Folder 17)
  - Dyer, Leonidas, 1928-1931 (Folder 18)
  - Earle, Ralph, 1932-1939 (Folder 19)
  - Eaton, Charles F., 1957-1960 (Folder 20)
  - Eaton, Cyrus S., 1951 (Folder 21)
  - Eberstadt, Ferdinand, 1946-1949 (Folder 22)
  - Edes, Louise B., 1953 (Folder 23)
  - Edison, Charles, 1960 (Folder 24)
  - The Educational Alliance, 1938-1962 (Folder 25)
  - Egan, Joseph L., 1945-1947 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Egan, Martin, 1929-1933 (Folder 2)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1949-1952 (Folder 3)
  - Eisenhower, Milton, 1954 (Folder 4)
  - The El Paso Times, 1954 (Folder 5)
  - Eller, E. M., 1946 (Folder 6)
  - Ellis, J. H. S., 1951-1956 (Folder 7)
  - Elman, Richard, 1959-1960 (Folder 8)
  - Emanuel, Victor
    - 1949-1953 (Folder 9)
    - 1954-1956 (Folder 10)
    - 1957-1960 (Folder 11)
  - Emergency Council to Keep the United States Out of Foreign War, 1939. Includes correspondence with Frank L. Williams and J. Harvie Williams (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Encyclopedia Americana, 1944-1945 (Folder 2)
  - Engelhard, Charles W., Mr. and Mrs., 1950-1962 (Folder 3)
  - Epstein, Benjamin, 1950-1959 (Folder 4)
  - Epstein, Eliahu, 1945-1948 (Folder 5)
  - Epstein, Julius, 1946-1960 (Folder 6)
  - Erbe, Henry H., 1938-1955 (Folder 7)
  - Eren, Nuren, 1958-1959 (Folder 8)
  - Ernst, Bernard M. L., 1935-1936 (Folder 9)
  - Ernst, Morris L., 1954-1955 (Folder 10)
  - Evans, W. H., 1960 (Folder 11)
  - Ewing, James L., III, 1953-1955 (Folder 12)
  - Facts On File, Inc., 1945-1951 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Fagan, Myron, 1951 (Folder 2)
  - Fain, J. T., 1945-1951 (Folder 3)
  - Fake, Guy L., 1951 (Folder 4)
  - Falk, Leo and Helen, 1940-1954 (Folder 5)
  - The Fargo Forum, 1944-1955 (Folder 6)
  - Faris, Barry, 1951-1960 (Folder 7)
  - Farley, James A.
    - 1942-1951 (Folder 8)
    - 1952-1962 (Folder 9)
  - Farnham, George, 1933-1934 (Folder 10)
  - Farrar, Strauss and Cudahy, Inc., 1938-1957 (Folder 11)
  - Faymonville, P. R., 1922-1923 (Folder 12)
  - Feild, Talbot, Jr., 1954-1962 (Folder 13)
  - Feller, Ralph M., 1960-1961 (Folder 14)
  - Felsher, Howard D., 1962 (Folder 15)
  - Felshin, Max, 1945-1947 (Folder 16)
  - Fensterstock, Barney B., 1951 (Folder 17)
  - Ferger, Roger, 1949-1962 (Folder 18)
  - Ferguson, Homer, 1946-1954 (Folder 19)
  - Ferrer, José, 1952-1959 (Folder 20)
  - Field, Elizabeth, 1931-1934 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Field, Frederick, 1930-1941 (Folder 2)
  - Field, George, 1946-1948 (Folder 3)
  - Fifield, James, Jr., 1946-1958 (Folder 4)
  - Finkelstein, Louis, 1944 (Folder 5)
  - Finley, Mark, 1962 (Folder 6)
  - Finneran, John F., 1950 (Folder 7)
  - Fish, Hamilton, 1946-1961 (Folder 8)
  - Fisher, Alphonse, 1947-1951 (Folder 9)
  - Fitch, George A., Mr. and Mrs.
    - 1932-1939 (Folder 10)
    - 1940-1951 (Folder 11)
  - FitzSimons, Paul, Mrs., 1941-1943 (Folder 12)
  - Flannelly, Joseph F., 1946-1950 (Folder 13)
  - Fleisher, B. W. (Box 50)
    - 1920-1922 (Folder 1)
    - 1923-1925 (Folder 2)
    - 1926-1942 (Folder 3)
  - Florence Morning News, 1953-1954 (Folder 4)
  - Flynn, John D., 1944-1959 (Folder 5)
  - Foley, Dan, 1959 (Folder 6)
  - Foley, John M., 1956-1962 (Folder 7)
  - Foley, Margaret T., 1950-1951 (Folder 8)
  - Fonda, George T., 1939-1958 (Folder 9)
  - Ford, Henry, II, 1953-1959 (Folder 10)
  - Ford, Julia Ellsworth, 1920-1932 (Folder 11)
  - Forrestal, James, 1947-1948 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Forster, Arnold
    - 1950-1954 (Folder 2)
    - 1955-1962 (Folder 3)
  - Foster, H. G., 1958-1959 (Folder 4)
  - Fox, Charles James, 1918-1956 (Folder 5)
  - Frank, Jerome N., 1939 (Folder 6)
  - Frankfurter, Felix, 1933-1935 (Folder 7)
  - Frankhauser, William, 1960-1961 (Folder 8)
  - Franklin, Lynn W., 1944 (Folder 9)
  - Franks, Maurice R., 1939-1959 (Folder 10)
  - Freedom Clubs, Inc., 1952-1956 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Freedoms Foundation, 1949-1958 (Folder 2)
  - The Freeman, 1950-1954. Includes correspondence with John Chamberlain, Henry Hazlitt, and Suzanne La Follette (Folder 3)
  - Freeman, Miller, 1945-1951 (Folder 4)
  - Frey, Robert L., 1948 (Folder 5)
  - Friend, J. L., 1950 (Folder 6)
  - Friendly, Alfred, 1961 (Folder 7)
  - Friendly, Edwin, 1942-1949 (Folder 8)
  - Fritz, Chester, Mr. and Mrs., 1921-1961 (Folder 9)
  - Frodel, Alfred C., 1950 (Folder 10)
  - Fu, Pearl, 1933-1940 (Folder 11)
  - Fuller, Samuel, 1951-1956 (Folder 12)
  - Gahagan, Andrew, 1946-1949 (Folder 13)
  - Gale, Oliver, 1953 (Folder 14)
  - Gall, John, 1943-1948 (Folder 15)
  - Gallagher, Hugh, 1950-1956 (Folder 16)
  - Gang, Martin, 1953-1956 (Folder 17)
  - Gannett, Lewis, 1926-1932 (Folder 18)
  - The Gannett Newspapers, Inc., 1939-1953 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Gannon, Robert I., 1942-1952 (Folder 2)
  - Gara, Helen, 1949 (Folder 3)
  - Gardner, Arthur, 1961-1962 (Folder 4)
  - Gardner, Rita N., 1961 (Folder 5)
  - Garey, Eugene, 1943-1953 (Folder 6)
  - Garrett, Paul, 1936-1957 (Folder 7)
  - Garrity, Devin, 1951-1961 (Folder 8)
  - Gatlin, Maurice, 1951-1957 (Folder 9)
  - Gavin, Thomas, 1951 (Folder 10)
  - Gehring, Frederic P., 1945-1962 (Folder 11)
  - Gerard, James, Mr. and Mrs., 1945-1951 (Folder 12)
  - Gibbons, Herbert Adams, 1931-1932 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Gibson, Hugh, 1939-1954 (Folder 2)
  - Gilbert, Rodney and Maude, 1921-1944 (Folder 3)
  - Gilliam, Charles E., 1960 (Folder 4)
  - Gilligan, William, 1942-1943 (Folder 5)
  - Gillis, James M., 1944-1955 (Folder 6)
  - Gimbel, Bernard F., 1956-1962 (Folder 7)
  - Giniger, K. S., 1953-1956 (Folder 8)
  - Ginsburg, Michael, 1951 (Folder 9)
  - Ginzburg, Benjamin, 1955-1959 (Folder 10)
  - Gipson, J. H., Sr., 1949-1956 (Folder 11)
  - Girdler, Tom, 1939-1948 (Folder 12)
  - Gitlow, Benjamin, 1940-1958 (Folder 13)
  - Glazer, Sidney, 1953 (Folder 14)
  - Glen Falls Post Co., 1950-1952 (Folder 15)
  - Glickman, Will, 1949-1962 (Folder 16)
  - Glover, Roy, Mr. and Mrs., 1940-1958 (Folder 17)
  - Glynn, Edward, 1942-1948 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Go, Yoshi, 1940-1951 (Folder 2)
  - Godley, K. M., 1959-1961 (Folder 3)
  - Goldbaum, Wenzel, 1954 (Folder 4)
  - Goldberg, Joshua and Henrietta
    - 1944-1953 (Folder 5)
    - 1954-1962 (Folder 6)
  - Goldberg, Rube, 1959 (Folder 7)
  - Goldenson, Leonard, 1960-1961 (Folder 8)
  - Golding, William, 1930-1951 (Folder 9)
  - Goldman, Albert, 1948-1951 (Folder 10)
  - Goldsmith, Lawrence, 1950 (Folder 11)
  - Goldstein, Abraham, 1941-1960 (Folder 12)
  - Goldstein, Nathaniel L., 1949-1951 (Folder 13)
  - Goldwater, Barry, 1955-1961 (Folder 14)
  - Goldwyn, Samuel, 1947-1950 (Folder 15)
  - Gordon, Arthur, 1923-1948 (Folder 16)
  - Gordon, Harry, 1946-1947 (Folder 17)
  - Gordon, Kenneth, 1948-1953 (Folder 18)
  - Gordon, Paul W., 1953 (Folder 19)
  - Gorman, Joseph J., 1949-1951 (Folder 20)
  - Goss, Bert, 1952-1961 (Folder 21)
  - Gould, George, 1953 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Gould, Gerald, 1951 (Folder 2)
  - Graf, Eugene, 1956 (Folder 3)
  - Graham, T. J., 1935-1953 (Folder 4)
  - Grand Street Boys' Association, 1939-1962 (Folder 5)
  - The Grand Rapids Herald, 1945-1955 (Folder 6)
  - Graves, John Temple, 1949-1951 (Folder 7)
  - Green, Glenn, 1949 (Folder 8)
  - Green, O. M., 1920-1959 (Folder 9)
  - Greenberg, J. W., 1950 (Folder 10)
  - Greenberg, Jae, 1955 (Folder 11)
  - Greene, Charles, 1955-1961 (Folder 12)
  - Greene, Jerome, 1930-1931 (Folder 13)
  - Greening, Cornell, 1937-1950 (Folder 14)
  - Greenman, Fred, 1942 (Folder 15)
  - Gregoor, Joseph A., 1939-1960 (Folder 16)
  - Griffen, C. Field, 1959 (Folder 17)
  - Griggs, Richard L., 1945 (Folder 18)
  - Grimes, Frank, 1947-1949 (Folder 19)
  - Grogan, Stanley J., 1958-1959 (Folder 20)
  - Grombach, John, 1952-1961 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Gross, Mark, 1945 (Folder 2)
  - Gross, William J., 1938 (Folder 3)
  - Grossbard, Sol, 1931-1942 (Folder 4)
  - Groves, Leslie R., 1947-1961 (Folder 5)
  - Gruber, W. R., 1948 (Folder 6)
  - Guerdan, Leon, 1942-1949 (Folder 7)
  - Guideposts Associates, Inc., 1945-1951 (Folder 8)
  - Guthman, Edwin O., 1962 (Folder 9)
  - Guylay, Richard, 1945-1950 (Folder 10)
  - Gwinn, Ralph W., 1943-1949 (Folder 11)
  - Habsburg, Otto von, 1953-1962 (Folder 12)
  - Hall, Howard, 1956-1960 (Folder 13)
  - Halton, Hugh, 1957-1959 (Folder 14)
  - Hawkes, Albert, 1938-1949 (Folder 15)
  - Hamilton, Arthur de C., 1918-1958 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Hansen, Carl O., 1956 (Folder 2)
  - Harding, Earl, Mr. and Mrs., 1938-1955 (Folder 3)
  - Harriss, Robert M.
    - 1946-1958 (Folder 4)
    - 1959-1962 (Folder 5)
  - Hart, Merwin K.
    - 1938-1944 (Folder 6)
    - 1945-1962 (Folder 7)
  - Hart, Vincent J., 1956 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Hartigan, John, 1946-1949 (Folder 2)
  - Hartnett, Vincent, 1951-1954 (Folder 3)
  - Hayes, Howland, 1948 (Folder 4)
  - Hays, Arthur Garfield, 1942-1952 (Folder 5)
  - Heaphy, J. David, 1955 (Folder 6)
  - Hearst, Randolph A., 1956-1960 (Folder 7)
  - Hearst, William Randolph, Jr.
    - 1949-1952 (Folder 8)
    - 1953-1962 (Folder 9)
  - Hearst, William Randolph, Sr., Mr. and Mrs., 1919-1958 (Folder 10)
  - Hearst Newspapers, 1947-1959 (Folder 11)
  - Heatwole, Oliver W., 1953-1956 (Folder 12)
  - Hedges, Frank, 1922-1935 (Folder 13)
  - Heintzleman, P. S., 1918-1922 (Folder 14)
  - Henderson, Arthur, 1957 (Folder 15)
  - Hennesy, James, 1954 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Hennings, Thomas C., Jr., 1955 (Folder 2)
  - Henry, James M., 1926 (Folder 3)
  - Henry, Natalie, 1936-1941 (Folder 4)
  - Herald Publishing Co., 1946-1948 (Folder 5)
  - Herbert, Maurice, 1962 (Folder 6)
  - Herbert Hoover Birthplace Foundation, 1954-1961 (Folder 7)
  - Hershey, John W., 1949-1962 (Folder 8)
  - Hevia, Carlos, 1954 (Folder 9)
  - Heydt, Charles, 1939-1940 (Folder 10)
  - Heymsfeld, Ralph, Mr. and Mrs., 1958-1961 (Folder 11)
  - Hickenlooper, Bourke B., 1950 (Folder 12)
  - Hicks, C. D., 1944 (Folder 13)
  - The High Point Enterprise, 1945-1950 (Folder 14)
  - Hill, John W.
    - 1934-1946 (Folder 15)
    - 1947-1962 (Folder 16)
  - Hill and Knowlton, Inc., 1938-1956 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Hillenkoetter, R. H., 1955 (Folder 2)
  - Hillman, Alex, 1948-1956 (Folder 3)
  - Hinshaw, David, 1943-1949 (Folder 4)
  - Hiss, Alger, 1946 (Folder 5)
  - Ho, George P., 1956 (Folder 6)
  - Hochschild, Harold K., 1930-1942 (Folder 7)
  - Hocking, William E., 1947-1948 (Folder 8)
  - Ho Tung, Robert, Sir, 1923-1933 (Folder 9)
  - Hodoroff, A., 1920-1926 (Folder 10)
  - Hoff, Syd, 1952-1953 (Folder 11)
  - Hoffman, Paul G., 1943-1950 (Folder 12)
  - Hoffmann, Frederick, 1950-1952 (Folder 13)
  - Hogan, Frank S., 1958 (Folder 14)
  - Holcombe, A. N., 1928-1946 (Folder 15)
  - Holdridge, Herbert C., 1954-1962 (Folder 16)
  - Holley, Cecile S., 1961 (Folder 17)
  - Holman, Frank E., 1953-1960 (Folder 18)
  - Hoopes, Alban, Mr. and Mrs., 1959-1961 (Folder 19)
  - Hoover, Alan, 1956 (Folder 20)
  - Hoover, Herbert (Box 62)
    - 1920-1935 (Folder 1)
    - 1936-1940 (Folder 2)
    - 1941-1945 (Folder 3)
    - 1946-1950 (Folder 4)
    - 1951-1955 (Folder 5)
    - 1956-1962 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Hoover, Herbert, Jr., 1956 (Folder 2)
  - Hoover, J. Edgar, 1961 (Folder 3)
  - Hoover Institution on War, Revolution and Peace (Folder 4)
  - 1957-1959
  - Hope, Walter, 1947 (Folder 5)
  - Hope, William C., 1959 (Folder 6)
  - Hopkinson, Harriet, 1932-1933 (Folder 7)
  - Hopper, Hedda, 1954-1962 (Folder 8)
  - Horan, Edward, 1951-1955 (Folder 9)
  - Horinouchi, Kensuke, 1932-1961 (Folder 10)
  - Hornbeck, Stanley, 1920-1962 (Folder 11)
  - House, Victor and Emily, 1938-1952 (Folder 12)
  - Houston, George H., 1938-1940 (Folder 13)
  - The Houston Chronicle, 1948-1958 (Folder 14)
  - Hoving, Walter, Mr. and Mrs., 1942-1960 (Folder 15)
  - Howard, Charles, 1961 (Folder 16)
  - Howard, Frederick M., 1928-1951 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Howard, Jack R., 1954-1962 (Folder 2)
  - Howard, Roy, 1925-1958 (Folder 3)
  - Howarth, Nelson O., 1953 (Folder 4)
  - Howland, Charles P., 1930-1932 (Folder 5)
  - Howlett, Walter M., 1948 (Folder 6)
  - Hoxter, Curtis J., 1952-1954 (Folder 7)
  - Hsieh, Tehyi, 1948 (Folder 8)
  - Hu, Shih
    - 1918-1927 (Folder 9)
    - 1928-1954 (Folder 10)
  - Hull, Cordell, 1934-1935 (Folder 11)
  - Human Events, 1955-1962. Includes correspondence with Frank C. Hanighen (Folder 12)
  - Hummel, John H., 1961 (Folder 13)
  - Humphrey, Hubert H., 1951-1957 (Folder 14)
  - Hunt, H. L., 1950-1960 (Folder 15)
  - Hunter, Edward, 1949-1960 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Hunter, Robert, Mr. and Mrs., 1940-1944 (Folder 2)
  - Huntington, Hugh, 1942-1946 (Folder 3)
  - Hurley, Patrick, 1949-1957 (Folder 4)
  - Hutchinson, Paul, 1932-1933 (Folder 5)
  - Hutton, Edward F., 1943-1959 (Folder 6)
  - Hyde, Arthur M., 1937 (Folder 7)
  - Illinois State Journal, 1948-1956 (Folder 8)
  - Ingebretsen, James C., 1951 (Folder 9)
  - Ingles, Elizabeth, 1958 (Folder 10)
  - Institute for Propaganda Analysis, 1940. Includes correspondence with Harold Lavine and Grayson N. Kefauver (Folder 11)
  - Institute of Pacific Relations, 1950-1951 (Folder 12)
  - Isaacs, Harold, 1955 (Folder 13)
  - Isaacs, Stanley M., 1937 (Folder 14)
  - Isaacson, Pauline, 1955-1956 (Folder 15)
  - Isenberg, Bill, 1954 (Folder 16)
  - Ishii, Mitsujero, 1960 (Folder 17)
  - Israels, Josef, II, 1944-1949 (Folder 18)
  - Ita, Mary, 1951-1957 (Folder 19)
  - Ivanoff, Peter, 1962 (Folder 20)
  - Ives, Burl, Mr. and Mrs., 1952-1954 (Folder 21)
  - Ives, Irving M., 1951-1957 (Folder 22)
  - Jackson, André A., 1958 (Folder 23)
  - Jacobs, J. E., 1932-1939 (Folder 24)
  - Jaffe, Charles, 1945-1951 (Folder 25)
  - Jamison, Robert H., 1961 (Folder 26)
  - Jansen, W. H., 1931-1937 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Jansen, William, 1950-1951 (Folder 2)
  - Japan. Ministry of Foreign Affairs, 1930 (Folder 3)
  - Japan Press Advertiser, 1924-1928 (Folder 4)
  - Jarvis, Guilbert, 1944-1945 (Folder 5)
  - Jeffreys, Raymond J., 1955-1956 (Folder 6)
  - Jenks, Jeremiah W., 1928-1929 (Folder 7)
  - Jessup, Philip C., 1948-1955 (Folder 8)
  - Jewish Publication Society of America, 1944-1960 (Folder 9)
  - Joffe, Jean, 1934-1949 (Folder 10)
  - Johnson, E. Quentin, 1948 (Folder 11)
  - Johnson, Edward, 1948 (Folder 12)
  - Johnson, Fred H., 1952-1953 (Folder 13)
  - Johnson, Larry, 1952-1960 (Folder 14)
  - Johnson, Louis, 1949-1956 (Folder 15)
  - Johnson, M. H., 1954 (Folder 16)
  - Johnson, Willard, 1942-1948 (Folder 17)
  - Johnston, Olin D., 1957 (Folder 18)
  - Jones, Daryl, 1960 (Folder 19)
  - Jones, Helen E., 1955 (Folder 20)
  - Jones, Jesse, 1945-1948 (Folder 21)
  - Jones, Miles W., 1940-1954 (Folder 22)
  - Jones, Robert F., 1950 (Folder 23)
  - Judge, Mary, 1954 (Folder 24)
  - Jung, Harry, 1937-1953 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Kahn, Florence P., 1941-1945 (Folder 2)
  - Kaiser, Henry J., 1945-1946 (Folder 3)
  - Kamei, Kanichiro, 1919-1928 (Folder 4)
  - Kane, John R., 1955-1961 (Folder 5)
  - Kannapolis Publishing Co., 1944-1951 (Folder 6)
  - Kapsner, Xavier, 1948-1949 (Folder 7)
  - Karger, Alfred Gus, 1961-1962 (Folder 8)
  - Kashins, Herman, 1959-1960 (Folder 9)
  - Kaufman, Irving R., 1951-1962 (Folder 10)
  - Kay, Robert H. C., 1943-1944 (Folder 11)
  - Kaye, Danny, Mrs., 1953-1954 (Folder 12)
  - Keig, Marshall, 1948 (Folder 13)
  - Kellems, Vivien, 1943-1960 (Folder 14)
  - Keller, Edward A., 1954-1957 (Folder 15)
  - Keller, James, 1941-1959 (Folder 16)
  - Kelley, Anna M., 1958 (Folder 17)
  - Kellogg, Florence, 1917-1934 (Folder 18)
  - Kelly, Bradley, 1961 (Folder 19)
  - Kelly, Eugene, 1952-1959 (Folder 20)
  - Kelly, John B., 1944-1950 (Folder 21)
  - Kelsey, Cadwallader, 1952 (Folder 22)
  - Kemmerer, Edwin, 1930-1945 (Folder 23)
  - Kenedy, Thomas B., 1955-1958 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Kennedy, Ardis M., 1944 (Folder 2)
  - Kennedy, Eunice, 1950 (Folder 3)
  - Kennedy, Joseph P., 1944-1960 (Folder 4)
  - Kennedy, R. D., 1961 (Folder 5)
  - Kennedy, Stephen P., 1956-1960 (Folder 6)
  - Kentucky New Era, 1950-1955 (Folder 7)
  - Keswick, John, 1930-1938 (Folder 8)
  - Keswick, W. J., 1930-1938 (Folder 9)
  - Ketchum, Carleton J., 1950 (Folder 10)
  - Kilcullen, James P., 1949-1954 (Folder 11)
  - Kilmer, Edward, 1954-1961 (Folder 12)
  - Kilmuir, Lord and Lady, 1955 (Folder 13)
  - Kindleberger, Charles P., 1947 (Folder 14)
  - Kinel, Lola, 1919-1937 (Folder 15)
  - King Features Syndicate. Includes correspondence with Ward Greene, F. J. Nicht, and various editors
    - 1944 (Folder 16)
    - 1945 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - 1946 (Folder 2)
    - 1947 (Folder 3)
    - 1948 (Folder 4)
    - 1949 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - 1950
      - January-June (Folder 2)
      - July-December (Folder 3)
    - 1951
      - January-June (Folder 4)
      - July-December (Folder 5)
    - 1952 (Box 71)
      - January-June (Folder 1)
      - July-December (Folder 2)
    - 1953 (Folder 3)
    - 1954 (Folder 4)
    - 1955 (Folder 5)
    - 1956 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - 1957 (Folder 2)
    - 1958-1959 (Folder 3)
    - 1960-1961 (Folder 4)
  - Kinney, Henry W., 1923-1957 (Folder 5)
  - Kirchner, James H., 1944-1951 (Folder 6)
  - Kirchhofer, Alfred, 1945-1956 (Folder 7)
  - Kirk, Myron, 1952 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Kirkpatrick, Ted, 1951-1952 (Folder 2)
  - Kiwanis Club of New York City, 1943-1960 (Folder 3)
  - Klein, Julius, 1949-1961 (Folder 4)
  - Kline, Ben G., 1924 (Folder 5)
  - Klinedinst, David M., 1954 (Folder 6)
  - Klopfer, Donald S., 1960 (Folder 7)
  - Kluckholn, Frank, 1956-1961 (Folder 8)
  - Knight, Frances G., 1951-1962 (Folder 9)
  - Knight, Margaret, 1932-1940 (Folder 10)
  - Knights of Columbus, 1952-1956 (Folder 11)
  - Knowland, William F., 1951-1960 (Folder 12)
  - Knowlton, Don, 1952 (Folder 13)
  - Kobe, John J., 1952-1956 (Folder 14)
  - Kohlberg, Alfred (Box 74)
    - 1944-1951 (Folder 1)
    - 1952-1953 (Folder 2)
    - 1954-1955 (Folder 3)
    - 1956-1957 (Folder 4)
    - 1958-1960 (Folder 5)
  - Kohlberg, Ida, 1960-1962 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Kohler, Herbert, 1937-1954 (Folder 2)
  - Kohler, Walter, 1935-1937 (Folder 3)
  - Kollek, Teddy, 1962 (Folder 4)
  - Komroff, Manuel, 1918-1943 (Folder 5)
  - Koo, T. Z., 1932 (Folder 6)
  - Koo, Wellington, Mr. and Mrs., 1931-1956 (Folder 7)
  - Koral, Daniel, 1955 (Folder 8)
  - Korb, T.W., 1958 (Folder 9)
  - Kornfeder, Joe, 1954 (Folder 10)
  - Kornitzer, Bela, 1960-1962 (Folder 11)
  - Krainukov, George T., 1944-1945 (Folder 12)
  - Kramer, Dale, 1939 (Folder 13)
  - Kreisler, Fritz, 1954-1956 (Folder 14)
  - Krueger, Karl, 1948-1951 (Folder 15)
  - Kuhn, Irene, 1942-1956 (Folder 16)
  - Kum, Keenseen, Mr. and Mrs., 1931-1933 (Folder 17)
  - Kung, H. H., Mr. and Mrs., 1928-1955 (Folder 18)
  - Kwei, C. S., 1953 (Folder 19)
  - Kwok, T. W., 1930-1956 (Folder 20)
  - La Follette, Suzanne, 1953 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Laird, John, 1950 (Folder 2)
  - Lamont, Corliss, 1940-1951 (Folder 3)
  - Lamont, Thomas
    - 1919-1920 (Folder 4)
    - 1921-1928 (Folder 5)
    - 1929-1948 (Folder 6)
  - Lancaster Newspapers, Inc., 1952-1960 (Folder 7)
  - Landenberger, Henry W., 1961 (Folder 8)
  - Landon, Alf, 1936-1957 (Folder 9)
  - Langhorne, George T., Mr. and Mrs., 1936-1952 (Folder 10)
  - Lasker, Mary, 1959-1960 (Folder 11)
  - Lasky, Victor
    - 1948-1951 (Folder 12)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - 1954-1957 (Folder 2)
  - Lathrop, Ann C., 1946-1947 (Folder 3)
  - Lawford, Pat, 1960-1962 (Folder 4)
  - Laymen's National Committee, 1946-1961 (Folder 5)
  - Lebeau, Frank, 1952 (Folder 6)
  - Lee, Ivy, Mr. and Mrs., 1929-1956 (Folder 7)
  - Lee, Morrie, 1959 (Folder 8)
  - Lefton, Al Paul, 1942-1951 (Folder 9)
  - Lehrbas, Lloyd, 1947 (Folder 10)
  - Leigh, W. Colston
    - 1934-1940 (Folder 11)
    - 1941-1942 (Folder 12)
  - Leikind, Seymour, 1944 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Leiper, Henry Smith, 1949 (Folder 2)
  - Leitzell, Ted, 1954 (Folder 3)
  - Léon, Maurice, 1943 (Folder 4)
  - Leopold, Helen, 1933-1951 (Folder 5)
  - Lequerica, José Felix de, 1949-1953 (Folder 6)
  - Leslie, Winifred, 1918-1924 (Folder 7)
  - Lesly, Philip, 1955 (Folder 8)
  - Lester, Mary, 1955-1960 (Folder 9)
  - Leung, George K., 1931-1932 (Folder 10)
  - Levi, Lawrence, 1959-1960 (Folder 11)
  - Levin, Y. Harry, 1954-1957 (Folder 12)
  - Levine, Isaac Don, 1936-1950 (Folder 13)
  - Levinthal, Sonia, 1959-1960 (Folder 14)
  - Levison, J. J., Mr. and Mrs., 1934-1946 (Folder 15)
  - Levison, Pearl, 1936-1939 (Folder 16)
  - Levitas, S. M., 1939-1961 (Folder 17)
  - Lewi, Maurice J., 1956 (Folder 18)
  - Lewin, Charles J., 1959-1960 (Folder 19)
  - Lewis, Arthur Baker, 1953 (Folder 20)
  - Lewis, John L., 1951-1952 (Folder 21)
  - Lewisohn, Ludwig, 1955 (Folder 22)
  - Lewison, Leah, 1918-1936 (Folder 23)
  - Lexington Herald-Leader, 1944-1959 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Li, K. C., 1937-1961 (Folder 2)
  - Li, Ming, 1930-1951 (Folder 3)
  - Li, Shun, 1919-1920 (Folder 4)
  - Li, Sum-ling, 1925 (Folder 5)
  - Liberty. Includes correspondence with Fulton Oursler
    - 1938-1939 (Folder 6)
    - 1940 (Folder 7)
    - 1941-1942 (Folder 8)
  - The Library of Congress, 1957 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Licensed Beverage Industries, Inc., 1960-1961 (Folder 2)
  - Liebman, Marvin, 1960-1962 (Folder 3)
  - Liebmann, Philip, 1952 (Folder 4)
  - Lilienthal, Alfred, 1942-1949 (Folder 5)
  - Lin, D. Y., 1919-1921 (Folder 6)
  - Lincoln, Edmund, 1939-1948 (Folder 7)
  - Lincoln Evening Courier, 1953-1954 (Folder 8)
  - Lindgren, Ethel, 1919-1939 (Folder 9)
  - Lipphard, William B., 1950 (Folder 10)
  - Lippmann, Walter, 1919-1936 (Folder 11)
  - Lipsky, Louis, 1933-1952 (Folder 12)
  - Lissman, Edward, 1957-1960 (Folder 13)
  - Lo, Wen Kan, 1928-1929 (Folder 14)
  - Lobinger, Charles, 1922-1934 (Folder 15)
  - Lockwood, Paul, 1943-1958 (Folder 16)
  - Lodge, George C., 1961 (Folder 17)
  - Lodge, Henry Cabot, Jr., 1935-1960 (Folder 18)
  - Lodge, John Davis, Mr. and Mrs., 1946-1960 (Folder 19)
  - Loeb, William, 1947-1962 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Logan, Edward, Mrs., 1946-1949 (Folder 2)
  - Loidolt, Rudolph, 1946 (Folder 3)
  - Lombard, Norman, 1953-1955 (Folder 4)
  - Lomer, Gerhard R., 1931 (Folder 5)
  - Longacre, C. S., 1947-1948 (Folder 6)
  - Longsdorf, George F., 1951 (Folder 7)
  - Longuevan, Joseph B., 1953-1962 (Folder 8)
  - Longworth, Nicholas, Mrs., 1944-1957 (Folder 9)